<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="no_help_available">
      There is no help available at this time.
    </string>
    <string name="about_help_topics">
      Help is available for each section of this app.
    </string>

    <string name="help_page_intro">
        We are here to help you!
        For information on the different parts of this app, touch any of the images below!</string>
    <string name="help_page_intro_html">
    <![CDATA[
      We are here to help you!
      For information on the different parts of this app, touch any of the images below!:
       ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section1">Profile</string>
    <string name="help_text_section1">
      Before you can join a game, you will have to create a profile, and provide the required credentials.
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section1">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        If you have an app that you want to add Help to, this demo app shows one way you can do that.
        All you need are two activities: one for the main Help screen and the other to display the Help
        text of a selected topic.
        </p>
      <p>Each of the help topics has a full page of help text.
        The help text is defined in xml files in the resource folders of the application.
        If you use CDATA in the xml definitions, you can define paragraphs and text in bold and italics.
        Links are also supported.
       </p>
      <p>
        Long topics can be scrolled. Try this one in both portrait and landscape orientation.
        You will probably have to scroll the text in landscape.
       </p>
      <p>
        If you want all the details about how this app was constructed,
        touch this link to open a web browser:
        <a href="http://blahti.wordpress.com">blahti blog</a>.
        </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
      ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section2">Map</string>
    <string name="help_text_section2">
     The Map view displays the location of your target 10 minutes ago.
        The location of your target will update every 10 minutes
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section2">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        You can display simple forms of Html in a text view.
        You use the Html class and its fromHtml static method.
        See
        <a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/android/text/Html.html">Html on Android Developers</a>.
      </p>
      <p>
        As shown here, paragraphs are supported,
        as are <b>bold text</b> and <i>italics</i>.
        The preceding paragraph has a link in it.
      </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="help_title_section3">Standings</string>
    <string name="help_text_section3">
      Standings shows who has been assassinated, and who is still in the game.
        Check to see who is dead, or is still alive
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section3">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
      You can define links in the help text strings.
      To get them to work, you have to do some extra set up in the code.
      </p>
      <p>
        To understand how to do this, study
        <a href="http://developer.android.com/reference/android/text/method/LinkMovementMethod.html">
          LinkMovementMethod</a> and how it is used with a TextView.
      </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section4">Join a game</string>
    <string name="help_text_section4">
      You have to join a game if you want to play. Games already in session can not be joined but you can join
        upcoming games.
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section4">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
      Image buttons define an image and a label on the screen.
      Touching an image takes you to the help text for a topic.
      </p>
      <p>
        For each button, you use three images.
        One represents the button in its default, unselected state.
        The other two are used for when the button is selected and pressed.
        The images and the definition of the button drawable are in the drawable folders in the resource folder.
        </p>
      <p>
        By the way, the images used in this demo app are left over from an
        <a href="http://blahti.wordpress.com/2011/03/14/build-dashboard-ui-for-android/">earlier demo program</a>.
        For a real app, choose images that are good fit for the help topics.
        </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>


</resources>